Division of Vertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Egg Data Slips, Series III
  - Egg Data Slips - P., 000021
    - Downy Woodpecker., 000553
    - Dunnock., 000597
    - Eastern Towhee., 000558
    - Eurasian Magpie., 000546
    - European Golden Plover., 000573
    - Fox Sparrow., 000501
    - Glossy Ibis., 000571
    - Gray Jay., 000515
    - Gray-Headed Chickadee., 000582
    - Great Cormorant., 000525
    - Great Kiskadee., 000567
    - Great Shearwater., 000602
    - Green-Tailed Towhee., 000557
    - Grey Partridge., 000513
    - Hairy Woodpecker., 000555
    - Harris' Hawk., 000494
    - Hepatic Tanager., 000560
    - Horned Grebe., 000576
    - House Sparrow., 000498
    - Indigo Bunting., 000505
    - Ivory Gull., 000492
    - Ladder-Backed Woodpecker., 000554
    - Laysan Albatross., 000538
    - Lazuli Bunting., 000502
    - Little Shearwater., 000601
    - Lousiana Waterthrush., 000495
    - Manx Shearwater., 000607
    - Mountain Chickadee., 000583
    - Neotropic Cormorant., 000524
    - Northern Waterthrush., 000496
    - Nuttall's Woodpecker., 000552
    - Osprey., 000493
    - Pachycephala., 000491
    - Painted Bunting., 000504
    - Parus., 000497
    - Passer montanus., 000499
    - Pelagic Cormorant., 000526
    - Periparus., 000514
    - Phainopepla., 000522
    - Phoenicurus., 000541
    - Phoenicurus., 000542
    - Phylloscopus., 000543
    - Pica hudsonia., 000544
    - Pied-Billed Grebe., 000579
    - Pine Grosbeak., 000556
    - Ploceus., 000572
    - Prinia., 000594
    - Progne subis., 000595
    - Purple Gallinule., 000591
    - Purple Martin., 000596
    - Pycnonotus., 000608
    - Pyrrhula., 000610
    - Red Billed Pigeon., 000508
    - Red Pharalope., 000530
    - Red-Billed Tropicbird., 000519
    - Red-Cockaded Woodpecker., 000550
    - Red-Faced Cormorant., 000528
    - Red-Necked Grebe., 000577
    - Red-Necked Grebe., 000578
    - Red-Necked Phalarope., 000531
    - Red-Tailed Tropicbird., 000521
    - Ring-Necked Pheasant., 000533
    - Rose-Breasted Grosbeak., 000534
    - Roseate Spoonbill., 000568
    - Savannah Sparrow., 000500
    - Scarlet Tanager., 000562
    - Short-Tailed Albatross., 000536
    - Snow Bunting., 000569
    - Sooty Albatross., 000539
    - Sooty Shearwater., 000603
    - Sora., 000592
    - Spotted Crake., 000593
    - Spotted Towhee., 000559
    - Steller's Eider., 000589
    - Summer Tanager., 000566
    - Three-toed Woodpecker., 000551
    - Varied Bunting., 000506
    - Vermillion Flycatcher., 000609
    - Vesper Sparrow., 000590
    - Wedge-Tailed Shearwater., 000606
    - Western Tanager., 000561
    - White-Crowned Pigeon., 000509
    - White-Faced Ibis., 000570
    - White-Faced Storm-Petrel., 000510
    - White-Headed Woodpecker., 000547
    - White-Tailed Tropicbird., 000520
    - Wilson's Phalarope., 000532
    - Yellow-Billed Magpie., 000545
  - Egg Data Slips - Q., 000022
    - Boat-Tailed Grackle., 000611
    - Common Grackle., 000613
    - Great-Tailed Grackle., 000612
  - Egg Data Slips - R., 000023
    - American Avocet., 000617
    - Bank Swallow., 000625
    - Black Skimmer., 000628
    - Black-Legged Kittiwake., 000627
    - Clapper Rail., 000616
    - Goldcrest., 000619
    - Golden-Crowned Kinglet., 000620
    - Greater Rhea., 000621
    - King Rail., 000614
    - McCown's Longspur., 000623
    - Red-Legged Kittiwake., 000626
    - Red-Winged Tinamou., 000624
    - Rhipidura., 000622
    - Ruby-Crowned Kinglet., 000618
    - Virginia Rail., 000615
  - Egg Data Slips - S., 000024
    - Allen's Hummingbird., 000640
    - American Goldfinch., 000682
    - American Redstart., 000659
    - American Tree Sparrow., 000684
    - American Woodcock., 000634
    - Ancient Murrelet., 000716
    - Arctic Tern., 000701
    - Barred Owl., 000705
    - Bay-Breasted Warbler., 000644
    - Black Phoebe., 000631
    - Black-Chinned Sparrow., 000685
    - Black-Throated Blue Warbler., 000643
    - Black-Throated Gray Warbler., 000653
    - Black-Throated Green Warbler., 000663
    - Blackburnian Warble., 000651
    - Blackpoll Warbler., 000660
    - Blue-Footed Booby., 000712
    - Brewer's Sparrow., 000686
    - Broad-tailed Hummingbird., 000638
    - Brown Booby., 000711
    - Brown Skua., 000693
    - Brown-Headed Nuthatch., 000669
    - Calliope Hummingbird., 000637
    - Cape May Warbler., 000661
    - Cerulean Warbler., 000645
    - Chestnut-Sided Warbler., 000655
    - Chipping Sparrow., 000688
    - Clay-Colored Sparrow., 000687
    - Common Eider., 000672
    - Common Ostrich., 000706
    - Common Tern., 000700
    - Craveri's Murrelet., 000717
    - Dickcissel., 000683
    - Eastern Bluebird., 000666
    - Eastern Meadowlark., 000707
    - Eastern Phoebe., 000632
    - Eurasian Woodcock., 000635
    - European Starling., 000709
    - Field Sparrow., 000689
    - Foster's Tern., 000699
    - Golden-cheeked Warbler., 000646
    - Great Gray Owl., 000703
    - Great Skua., 000697
    - Hooded Siskin., 000679
    - Hooded Warbler., 000647
    - King Eider., 000673
    - Lawrence's Goldfinch., 000678
    - Least Tern., 000702
    - Lesser Goldfinch., 000681
    - Long-Tailed Jaeger., 000694
    - Magnolia Warbler., 000652
    - Masked Booby., 000710
    - Mountain Bluebird., 000664
    - Northern Hawk Owl., 000714
    - Northern Parula., 000642
    - Northern Rough-Winged Sparrow., 000692
    - Ovenbird., 000636
    - Palm Warbler., 000654
    - Parasitic Jaeger., 000695
    - Pine Siskin., 000680
    - Pine Warbler., 000657
    - Pomarine Jaeger., 000696
    - Prairie Warbler., 000649
    - Pygmy Nuthatch., 000670
    - Red-Breasted Nuthatch., 000667
    - Red-Breasted Sapsucker., 000675
    - Red-Footed Booby., 000713
    - Red-Naped Sapsucker., 000674
    - Rock Wren., 000629
    - Roseate Tern., 000698
    - Rudous Hummingbird., 000639
    - Saxicola., 000630
    - Say's Phoebe., 000633
    - Serinus., 000641
    - Spectacled Eider., 000671
    - Sporophila., 000690
    - Spotted Owl., 000704
    - Stagonopleura., 000691
    - Sylvia., 000715
    - Townsend's Warbler., 000662
    - Tropical Parula., 000658
    - Western Bluebird., 000665
    - Western Meadowlark., 000708
    - White-Breasted Nuthatch., 000668
    - Williamson's Sapsucker., 000676
    - Xantus's Murrelet., 000718
    - Yellow Warbler., 000656
    - Yellow-Bellied Sapsucker., 000677
    - Yellow-Rumped Warbler., 000648
    - Yellow-Throated Warbler., 000650
  - Egg Data Slips - T., 000025
    - American Robin., 000756
    - Barn Owl., 000768
    - Bendire's Thrasher., 000735
    - Bewick's Wren., 000731
    - Brown Thrasher., 000742
    - California Thrasher., 000741
    - Carolina Wren., 000732
    - Cassin's Kingbird., 000767
    - Collared Brushturkey., 000724
    - Common Redshank., 000747
    - Common Shelduck., 000723
    - Couch's Kingbird., 000762
    - Crissal Thrasher., 000737
    - Curve-Billed Thrasher., 000738
    - Eastern Kingbird., 000765
    - Elegant Tern., 000727
    - Elegant Trogon., 000752
    - Eurasian Blackbird., 000755
    - Eurasian Wren., 000751
    - Gray Kingbird., 000763
    - Gray Thrasher., 000736
    - Greater Prairie-Chicken., 000760
    - Greater Yellowlegs., 000744
    - House Wren., 000748
    - LeConte's Thrasher., 000739
    - Least Grebe., 000719
    - Lesser Yellowlegs., 000743
    - Long-Billed Thrasher., 000740
    - Mistle Thrush., 000759
    - Pacific Wren., 000750
    - Redwing., 000754
    - Ring Ouzel., 000758
    - Royal Tern., 000729
    - Ruddy Shelduck., 000722
    - Scissor-Tailed Flycatcher., 000764
    - Sharp-Tailed Grouse., 000761
    - Solitary Sandpiper., 000746
    - Song Thrush., 000757
    - Tetrao., 000725
    - Thalasseus maximus., 000728
    - Thamnophilus., 000730
    - Tiaris., 000733
    - Todirostrum., 000734
    - Tree Swallow., 000720
    - Turdoides., 000753
    - Violet-Green Swallow., 000721
    - Western Kingbird., 000766
    - Willet., 000745
    - Winter Wren., 000749
    - Yellow-Nosed Albatross., 000726
  - Egg Data Slips - U., 000026
    - Common Murre., 000769
    - Thick-Billed Murre., 000770
  - Egg Data Slips - V., 000027
    - Bell's Vireo., 000776
    - Black-Capped Vireo., 000775
    - Black-Whiskered Vireo., 000774
    - Blue-Headed Vireo., 000785
    - Blue-Winged Warbler., 000773
    - Cassin's Vireo., 000777
    - Golden-Winged Warbler., 000772
    - Gray Vireo., 000786
    - Hutton's Vireo., 000781
    - Northern Lapwing., 000771
    - Philadelphia Vireo., 000783
    - Plumbeous Vireo., 000784
    - Red-Eyed Vireo., 000782
    - Warbling Vireo., 000779
    - White-Eyed Vireo., 000780
    - Yellow-Throated Vireo., 000778
  - Egg Data Slips - W., 000028
  - Egg Data Slips - X, Y, Z., 000029
    - Golden-Crowned Sparrow., 000792
    - Harris' Sparrow., 000794
    - Mourning Dove., 000790
    - Sabine's Gull., 000788
    - White-Crowned Sparrow., 000793
    - White-Throated Sparrow., 000791
    - White-Winged Dove., 000789
    - Yellow-Headed Blackbird., 000787
  - Egg Data Slips. Miscellaneous., 001238
    - Accipitridae. Data slips., 001273
    - Alcids. Data slips., 001251
    - Anatidae. Data slips., 001271
    - Anhingas. Data slips., 001266
    - Blackbirds. Data slips., 001263
    - Caprimulgids. Data slips., 001255
    - Cormorants. Data slips., 001265
    - Cranes. Data slips., 001244
    - Cuckoos. Data slips., 001253
    - Egg Data Slip. Egg data slip from cigar box # 1., 001318
    - Egg Data Slip. Egg data slip from cigar box # 2., 001319
    - Egg Data Slip. Egg data slip from cigar box # 3., 001320
    - Egg Data Slip. Original data for eggs packed in a miscellaneous cigar box. Photocopies are included with eggs., 001321
    - Egg Data. Miscellaneous egg data slips. Photocopies with eggs., 001324
    - Egg Data. Oological Collection data slips., 001428
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 2.., 001223
    - Egg Labels. Eggs from this clutch ar No. Orn.E.00847. This photocopied data slip was found in a case of nests, though no nest was with it., 001224
    - Egg Labels. Label from discarded eggshell., 001225
    - Egg Labels. Not researched., 001227
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 1., 001228
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 3., 001229
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 4., 001230
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 5., 001231
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 6., 001232
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 7., 001233
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 8., 001234
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 9., 001235
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 10., 001236
    - Egg Labels. Data slips - no eggs. H Lost, page 11., 001237
    - Egg Labels. Stray labels from egg drawers, no associated with specific eggs., 001277
    - Egg Labels. Brockway's Notes on Bird eggs. These specimens were not in the collection given to YPM., 001278
    - Egg Labels. Stray labels from egg drawers, no associated with specific eggs., 001279
    - Egg Labels., 001280
    - Egg Labels. Slips were in Pratt Case, but not associated with eggs., 001281
    - Egg Labels. Slip and list were in a drawer with mostly Havemeyer nests (some Brockway)., 001282
    - Egg Labels., 001283
    - Falconidae. Data slips., 001274
    - Finches. Data slips., 001260
    - Flycatchers. Data slips., 001264
    - Fulmar. Data slips., 001239
    - Grebes. Data slips., 001261
    - Gulls & Terns. Data slips., 001250
    - Harry Merrill Collection Labels. Original labels of the Harry Merrill Collection of Birds Eggs., 001221
    - Herons. Data slips., 001245
    - Hummingbird. Data slips., 001257
    - Ibis. Data slips., 001268
    - Kemp Collection. 1 page of miscellaneous data from kemp collection eggs/nests., 001323
    - Loons. Data slips., 001267
    - Miscellaneous Bird Labels., 001222
    - Osprey. Data slips., 001272
    - Owls. Data slips., 001254
    - Oyster catchers. Data slips., 001247
    - Partial Egg Data. Partial egg data for miscellaneous eggs/nests., 001322
    - Pelicans. Data slips., 001262
    - Penguins. Data slips., 001240
    - Phalaropes. Data slips., 001249
    - Pigeons. Data slips., 001252
    - Plovers. Data slips., 001246
    - Rails. Data slips., 001243
    - Sandpipers. Data slips., 001248
    - Storks. Data slips., 001269
    - Swift. Data slips., 001256
    - Tanager. Data slips., 001259
    - Terns/Gulls. Data slips., 001241
    - Tetraonidae. Data slips., 001275
    - Tinamous. Data slips., 001242
    - Vultures. Data slips., 001270
    - W.C. Hanna Collection Labels., 001226
    - Warblers. Data slips., 001276
    - Woodpecker. Data slips., 001258
- Ledgers, Catalogs, Inventories, Series IV
  - Bishop., 000564
    - Oological Catalog of Louis B. Bishop., 1881-1934; 000565
  - Divisional Catalog Ledgers., 001426
  - Egg Catalog. Inventory off eggs in the old Zoology Catalog., 001335
  - Recataloged Specimens. List of recataloged specimens with their new numbers., 001362
- Collector Field Notes, Catalogs, etc., Series V
  - Archer, Anthony L. Field Notes, Kenya., 1965; 000880
  - Asplund, Kenneth. Field notebook. Appalachian Mountains - Okefenokee Swamp Expedition., 1961; 000876
  - Bacon, Paul G. Inventory, labels, etc., 001326
  - Bacon, Ross. Labels, notes, etc. from the Bacon Egg Collection., 001325
  - Ball, Stanley C. Miscellaneous notes., 000877
  - Bishop, Louis B. Bird Egg Collection inventory, etc. 3 folders., 000879
  - Bishop, Marshall B. Field notes., 000878
  - Campbell, John H. & Richard D. Campbell. Inventory Skin & Skulls., 000881
  - Capainolo, Peter A. New York Red Squirrels., 2008-2009; 000882
  - Dickerman, Robert W. FIeld notes., 1956-1961; 000883
  - Dodson, Stanley I. FIeld notes., 1963; 000884
  - Eastman, Joseph T. Field and lab notebooks from J. T. Eastman's work on Antarctic fishes., 001449
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Green Record book from Federal Supply Service labeled "NBP 96-6". Contains field data from the R/V Nathaniel B. Palmer, Cruise 96-6. Lyttelton, NZ- McMurdo 11 Dec 1996-8 Jan 1997. Contains specimen data from Antarctic fishes at McMurdo. Includes histology of specimens. There are inter-mixed blank pages, but the entire book is used., 001454
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Black and red ledger labeled "LMG 01-05". Contains data from the ARSV Laurence M. Gould, Cruise 01-05, 11 June-16 July 2001. Punta Arenas. Fishing near Palmer Station, Brabant Island and Low Island. Includes data on bouyancy and morphology. Microfil procedures and Alizarin staining. There are many blank pages., 11 June 2001 - 16 July 2001; 001459
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Black and red ledger labeled "NBP 04-04, ICEFISH Cruise". Contains data from NBP 04-04 ICEFISH Cruise 17 May 2004-17 July 2004 Punta Arenas to Cape Town. Contains notes on stations and localities as well as Microfil data for Eleginops and others. Includes data on specimens skeletonized., 001460
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Black and red ledger labeled "NBP 04-04 ICEFISH Histology". Data from the NBP 04-04 ICEFISH Cruise, Histology Results. Includes data on a variety of taxa collected and examined histologically. Several references to photographs., 17 May 2004 - 17 July 2004; 001461
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Notebook entitled "Fishes #2". Contains fish data from Antarctica. Dates are in the 1960's and 1970's., 1963-1977; 001451
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Notebook entitled "Fishes #1". Contains some fish data from Antarctica. The remainder of the book contains data on fishes from elsewhere. Dates are in 1974., 001450
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Ledger (notebook) containing data on fishes from Antarctica including mostly dates in the 1980's. Many blank pages are intermixed, but the full ledger appears to be used. Includes morphological data from specimens at National Museum of New Zealand and the University of Michigan., 1978-1994; 001452
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Green Record book from Federal Supply Service labeled "McMurdo- 1986". Includes morphological and specimen data from Antarctic fishes at McMurdo. Some information on hystology is included, such as the stains used and which specimens are sectioned. Book is blank after page 143., 001453
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Green field book from Federal Supply Service labeled "McMurdo 1991" with logo of Antarctica and a penguin on the cover. Includes specimen data, histology notes, tissue freezing experiments and observations on aquarium specimens at McMurdo. Pages after 117 are blank., 001455
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Green field book from Federal Supply Service labeled "Eastman McMurdo 1995". Includes buoyancy data and histology technique data for several taxa of Antarctic fishes as well as data for specimens perfused with either Bouin's solution or Microfil. Pages after 49 are blank., 001456
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Black and red ledger labeled "NBP 97-9 Ross Sea". Includes data from the NBP Cruise 97-9, 20 December 1997-10 Jan 1998 of the Southwestern Ross Sea, ice edge to McMurdo. 2nd Roaverrs Cruise. Bouyancy data are included. Includes detailed drawings of sampling locations and drawings of stingrays and fish fins as illustrations of morphology., 001457
    - Eastman, Joseph T. Black and red ledger labeled "Research, 2003-2010 Histology". Includes histology data on a variety of specimens of Antarctic fishes. Includes drawings and references to photographs. Many blank pages intermixed, but the entire book is used., 001458
  - Fox, Stanley F. FIeld notes., 000885
  - Garber, Steve D. Field notes. Mexico., 1974-1975; 000886
  - Gauthier, Jacques A. Miscellaneous notes., 2001; 000887
  - Gentry, Howard S. Inventory, Mexico & California., 000888
  - Handsaker, Ralph W. Egg collection labels., 000889
    - Handsaker Collection. Egg and nest data labels. - Miscellaneous., 001215
    - Handsaker Collection. Egg and nest data labels. - Passerines., 001216
    - Handsaker Collection. Egg and nest data labels. - Non-Passerines., 001217
    - Handsaker Collection. Data cards for specimens not in the collection., 001218
    - Handsaker Collection. Miscellaneous paperwork., 001219
  - Hansen, David P. Collection from Costa Rica, 1964., 001351
  - Havemeyer, Henry O. Havemeyer Egg collection Inventory., 000890
  - Havemeyer, Henry O. File and correspondence on the aquisition of the Havemeyer Egg Collection., 000891
  - Hibbs B.J. & G.R. Hibbs. Inventory., 000892
  - Hibbs, George R. & Barbara J. Hibbs. List of specimens collected during the summer of 1962 from Oregon, Colorado and Utah., 001352
  - Hoesch, Walter & Donald H. Selchow. Inventory, Africa., 000893
  - Johnson, W.B. Inventory., 000894
  - Kalinowski, Celestino. Inventory., 000895
  - Kiff, Lloyd. Egg collection Inventory., 001334
  - Lazell, James D. Miscellaneous notes, correspondence., 000896
  - Leenders, Anton A., 000897
  - Ligon, J. S. Inventory., 000898
  - Loke Wan Tho - Harrisson Bird Collection. Bird Collection Inventory, Borneo., 000899
  - Loveyjoy, Thomas E. Inventory., 000900
  - MacArthur, Robert. Inventory., 000901
  - Minter, D. M. Inventory, Kenya., 000902
  - Moore, Jon A. Miscellaneous notes., 000903
  - Morrill, Ralph C. Inventory., 000904
  - Munro, James A. Inventory., 000905
  - Olalla, Carlos. Notes, Corespondence, etc relating to the Olalla Collection., 000906
  - Paynter, Raymond A. Inventory., 000907
  - Peterson, R. I. Inventory., 000908
  - Pospisil, Leopold J. Inventory., 000909
  - Racey, Kenneth. Journal., 1935-1953; 000910
  - Rathborne, J.Cornelius & Phillip S. Carr. Inventory., 000911
  - Reed, Charles, A. Persian mammals list., 001353
  - Remington, Charles L. & Eric E. Remington. Correspondence, catalogs, field catalogs, etc., 000912
    - Remington, Charles L. Correspondence, USA, 1964; 000919
    - Remington, Charles L. Correspondence, USA, 1965; 000920
    - Remington, Charles L. Correspondence, Canada, 1965; 000921
    - Remington, Charles L. Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965; 000922
    - Remington, Charles L. Miscellaneous., 1965; 000923
    - Remington, Charles L. Mammal correspondence, 000913
    - Remington, Eric. E. Mammal catalog, 1958-1967; 000914
    - Remington, Eric. E. Field Notes, 1964; 001339
    - Remington, Eric. E. Field catalog, 1965; 000916
    - Remington, Eric. E. Field catalog, 1965; 000917
    - Remington, Eric. E. Field notebooks., 000915
    - Remington, Eric. E. Inventory, 000918
  - Ripley, Sydney D. Indonesia bird skin inventory., 000924
  - Selchow, Donald H. Inventory., 000925
  - Shpak, Maxim. Field notes, Osteo inventory., 000926
  - Simmons, Elliot R. Inventory., 000927
  - Smith, Krister T. Field Notes., 2001; 000928
  - Uzzell, Thomas M. Inventory., 1971; 000929
  - Valentine, Joseph M. Field Notes., 1923-1924; 000930
  - Van Devender, R. Wayne. Field Notes., 000931
  - Walker, Alexander. Inventory., 000932
  - Watson, George E. Inventory., 000933
  - Paulay, Gustav., 001432
- Maps, Series VI
  Maps from various states, countries, continants and world.
  - Africa., 000983
  - Alabama., 000935
  - Alaska., 000936
  - Antarctica., 000984
  - Arizona., 000937
  - Arkansas., 000938
  - Asia., 000985
  - Australia., 000986
  - Austria., 000987
  - California., 000939
  - Canada., 000988
  - Central America., 000989
  - Colorado., 000940
  - Connecticut., 000941
  - Costa Rica., 000990
  - Delaware., 000942
  - Europe., 000991
  - Florida., 000943
  - France., 000992
  - Guatamala., 000993
  - Hawaii., 000944
  - Illinois., 000945
  - Indiana., 000946
  - Iowa., 000947
  - Italy., 000994
  - Kansas., 000948
  - Kentucky., 000949
  - Lousiana., 000950
  - Maine., 000951
  - Mars., 000995
  - Maryland., 000952
  - Massachusetts., 000953
  - Mexico., 000996
  - Michigan., 000954
  - Minnesota., 000955
  - Mississippi., 000956
  - Missouri., 000957
  - Montana., 000958
  - Nebraska., 000959
  - Nevada., 000960
  - New Guinea., 000997
  - New Hampshire., 000961
  - New Jersey., 000962
  - New Mexico., 000963
  - New York., 000964
  - Nigeria., 000998
  - North Carolina., 000965
  - North Dakota., 000966
  - Ohio., 000967
  - Oklahoma., 000968
  - Oregon., 000969
  - Pennsylavania., 000970
  - Philippines., 000999
  - Rhode Island., 000971
  - Russia., 001000
  - South Carolina., 000972
  - Switzerland., 001001
  - Tennessee., 000973
  - Texas., 000974
  - Trinadad., 001002
  - United States., 000982
  - Utah., 000975
  - Venezuela., 001003
  - Vermont., 000976
  - Virginia., 000977
  - Washington., 000978
  - West Virgina., 000979
  - Wisconsin., 000980
  - World., 001005
  - Wyoming., 000981
  - Yugoslavia., 001004
- Collecting Permits, Series VII
  - Alabama. Past Alabama collecting permits., 001008
  - Arizona. Past Arizona collecting permits., 001009
  - Arkansas. Past Arkansas collecting permits., 001010
  - California. Past California collecting permits., 001011
  - Connecticut. Past Connecticut collecting permits., 001012
  - Federal Permit. Information on Federal Collecting permit., 001357
  - Federal. Past federal collecting permits., 001007
  - Florida. Past Florida collecting permits., 001013
  - Georgia. Past Georgia collecting permits., 001014
  - Hawaii. Past Hawaii collecting permits., 001015
  - Illinois. Past Illinois collecting permits., 001016
  - Indiana. Past Indiana collecting permits., 001017
  - Iowa. Past Iowa collecting permits., 001018
  - Kansas. Past Kansas collecting permits., 001019
  - Kentucky. Past Kentucky collecting permits., 001020
  - Louisiana. Past Louisiana collecting permits., 001021
  - Maine. Past Maine collecting permits., 001023
  - Maryland. Past Maryland collecting permits., 001022
  - Massachusetts. Past Massachusetts collecting permits., 001024
  - Michigan. Past Michigan collecting permits., 001025
  - Minnesota. Past Minnesota collecting permits., 001026
  - Mississippi. Past Mississippi collecting permits., 001027
  - Missouri. Past Missouri collecting permits., 001028
  - New Hampshire. Past New Hampshire collecting permits., 001029